partstore.com 2009-06-25

# PartStore.com's Privacy Policy

| 

PartStore.com realizes that customers are concerned about how the information they provide online will be used. This privacy policy will address those concerns. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We may use the information that we collect about you online to process your order and provide a more personalized shopping experience. 

When placing an order, we ask you to provide information online including your name, mailing address, e-mail address and credit card information. All information is stored on a highly secured server that is not accessible through the Internet. 

To continuously assess the value of our online shopping experience, we may track the way customers use our site; however, this information is analyzed only in the aggregate and not at the individual level. To this end, the information you provide us will help us tailor our communications and product offerings so that you receive more of what you want and less of what you don't want when shopping with us. 

We will not rent or sell your email address without your consent, and do not send promotional emails to anyone on our "Do Not Send" list. 

We may notify you from time to time of special offers and information via e-mail that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may include yourself on our "Do Not Send" list by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email you have received. Even so, you may continue to receive non-marketing messages from us (for example, messages regarding Website technical and security issues or delivery information), and you cannot opt-out of receiving such non-marketing messages. We also reserve the right, from time to time, to re-contact former users of our Websites. 

We may use your information for these purposes: 

  * To deliver services, such as educational programs, information, newsletters or software you request or purchase;
  * To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from us, or other third parties, or to forward promotional materials;
  * To complete a transaction or service requested by you;
  * To fulfill the terms of a promotion;
  * To ensure the Sites are relevant to your needs;
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you; 
  * To notify you about a material change to this privacy policy or the Visitor Agreement, if necessary;
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of the Sites; and
  * To contact you in response to sign up forms such as Contact Us or Order Inquiry.

If you do not wish to receive catalogues from us or any third parties, please email us at [nocatalogues@partstore.com](mailto:nocatalogues@partstore.com)

PartStore.com may update its privacy policy periodically and use of the information we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. If a change is made, we will post the updated policy on this site and we encourage you to periodically check our policy. By using our website after change in the privacy policy is made, you consent to the updated policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
